#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-hoang-0bb978178 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Coaching & Mentoring
Functional Programming
Representational State Transfer
(REST)

# Nguyen Hoang

Software Developer at NAVER VIETNAM Vietnam

## Summary

Objective: Become a Technical Architecture after 5 - 7 years in my job.

Four years of experience working in Web Development.

Four years 6 months of experience working with ReactJS.

One year of experience working with NodeJS.

One year of experience working with Unit Test.

One year of experience working with MongoDB.

Other Skills: C/C++, C#, Github.

# Experience

NAVER VIETNAM
Senior Software Engineer
January 2022 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

JourneyHorizon Senior Software Engineer February 2020 - January 2022 (2 years) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Orient Software Development Corp. Software Engineer April 2019 - February 2020 (11 months)

KMS Technology, Inc.
Software Engineer
January 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 4 months)

### Education

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering · (2013 - 2018)